In America’s forgotten war, they made history.
Devotion is a war, drama, action film directed by J.D. Dillard.
The harrowing true story of two elite US Navy
fighter pilots during the Korean War.
Their heroic sacrifices would ultimately make them
the Navy's most celebrated wingmen.
Jesse Brown, played by Jonathan Majors.
Thomas J. Hudner Jr., played by Glen Powell.
Daisy Brown, played by Christina Jackson.
Dick Cevoli, played by Thomas Sadoski.
Bill Koenig, played by Daren Kagasoff.
Marty Goode, played by Joe Jonas.
Devotion is a 2022 American biographical war film based on Devotion: An Epic Story of Heroism, Friendship,
and Sacrifice by Adam Makos, which shows the comradeship between naval officers Jesse L.
Brown and Tom Hudner during the Korean War.
Directed by J.
Dillard and written by Jake Crane and Jonathan Stewart, it stars Jonathan Majors as Brown and Glen Powell as Hudner, with
Christina Jackson, Daren Kagasoff, Joe Jonas, Nick Hargrove, Spencer Neville, and Thomas Sadoski in supporting roles.
Devotion premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival in IMAX at the Ontario Place Cinesphere on September 12, 2022,
and was released by Columbia Pictures through Sony Pictures Releasing in the United States on November 23, 2022.
While it received positive reviews from critics and audiences, it was a box-office
bomb, grossing only $21.8 million worldwide against a $90 million budget.
The film explores themes of korean war (1950-53), based on true
story, aftercreditsstinger, duringcreditsstinger, war.
The tone is emotional.